Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Associations
  - American Pain Society. Organizational meetings, 1977. (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. B.B. Wolff, Pres., 1977. (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - American Pain Society. Standards Committee Pro Tem, 1977-1978. (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - American Pain Society. General correspondence, 1977-1984. (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - American Pain Society. General correspondence, 1977-1984. (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. B.B. Wolff, 1978. (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - American Pain Society. Board of Directors meeting, 1978. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. B.B. Wolff, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - American Pain Society. Midwest Pain Society, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. W. Willis, Treasurer, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - American Pain Society. Education Committee, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - American Pain Society. Public Information Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - American Pain Society. CMTE Guidelines Organization of Pain Centers, 1979-1983. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - American Pain Society. Western USA Pain Society, Western Region APS, 1979-1987. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. B.B. Wolff, 1980. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. Crue, 1980. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - American Pain Society. Board of Directors/Annual Business Meeting minutes, 1980. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - American Pain Society. By-Laws, 1980-1981. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - American Pain Society. Business Meeting minutes, 1981. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. F. Battista, Secretary, 1981. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. Crue, 1981. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. B.B. Wolff, 1981. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. Crue, 1982. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence with Dr. Sweet, 1982. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - American Pain Society. Preliminary directory, 1982. (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - American Pain Society. Directory, 1983-1984. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence, Dr. Willis, 1983-1985. (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - American Pain Society. General correspondence, 1985-1992. (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - American Pain Society. By-Laws, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - American Pain Society. Pain Data, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence [folder added late], 1977 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence [folder added late], 1978 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence [folder added late], 1979 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - American Pain Society. Correspondence [folder added late], 1980 (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - American Society for Clinical Pharmacology and Therapeutics. Correspondence, 1970-1982. (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - American Society for Pharmacology and Experimental Therapeutics. 1967-1989. (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Anesthesia Code, 1945-(1960?). (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. General, 1947-1957. (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. "Anesthesiology" Journal, 1950-1956. (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting, Seattle, 1953. (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting, Cincinnati, 1954. (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committees, 1954-1957. (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Newsletter, 1954-1957. (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Board of Directors, 1954-1958. (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Board of Directors, 1954-1958. (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting, Boston, 1955. (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. "Clinical Investigation of Local Anesthetic Drugs." Bonica & Hadfield, Kansas City, MO, 1956. (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting, Kansas City, 1956. (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive Committee, 1956-1957. (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting, Los Angeles, 1957. (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Los Angeles, 1957. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Presidency - Dan Moore, 1957. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Chicago, 1957. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Reference Committee on By-Laws, 1957-1960. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on Maternal Welfare, 1957-1960. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. General correspondence, 1957-1963. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committees, general, 1957-1965. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Building Fund Committee, 1959-1960. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Board of Directors, 1961. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on Clarification of Ethics, 1961. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Research Committee, 1961. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. President-elect, Board of Direct., House of Deleg., 1965. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. President - Elect Report, 1965. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Newsletters, 1966-1969. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Wood Library - Museum, 1966-1981. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on Residencies, 1968. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Manpower in Anesthesia, 1969-1973. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. General Correspondence, 1970-1975. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Past Presidents - Photo, 1972. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Acupuncture Ad Hoc Advisory Committee, 1972-1977. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. John Andes, Executive Secretary, 1972-1979. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Calendar, 1975-1990. (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Distinguished Service Award Committee, 1976. (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Refresher Course "Current Concepts of Pain Mech.", 1977. (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Pain Clinic Directory, 1977. (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. UW Alumni Reception, 1977. (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Newsletter, 1977-1978. (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. General Correspondence, 1979. (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Annual meeting - Did Not Attend, 1981. (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Directory, 1981, 1984. (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Newsletter, 1981-1990. (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - American Society of Chinese Medicine. 1973. (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. 1974-1978. (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Eltherington: Protocol for Study to Examine Use., 1976. (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Kraynack: Studies of the Regulation of Lidocaine., 1976-1977. (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Guidelines for Submission of Research Grants, 1976-1977. (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Rowlingson: Systemic Analgesic Effects of Local..., 1977. (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. B.J. Kraynack: Dibutyryl Cyclic AMP & Tetrodoxin, 1977-1978. (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Tark: Comparison of efficacy of Etidocaine to Xylocaine., 1978. (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. San Francisco, 1979-1980. (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. [Correspondence], 1979-1991. (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Photos, 1993. (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Anesthesia Foundation. 1973-1977. (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Anesthesia History Association. 1984-1991. (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Anesthesia Memorial Foundation. n.d. (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Site Visit Presentation, 1972. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Evaluation of Overall Program, 1972. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Evaluation, 1)Full text 2)Emily Black, 1973. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Misc. Material, 1974. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Anestheisa Research Center, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Site Visit Presentation, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Obstetric Anesthesia Section, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Regional Anesthesia Section, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. General Corres., 1977. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. History, Development, Future Needs, and Status, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Anesthesiology in the USA, 1975, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Introduction on Research - Regional Anesthesia..., 1977. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Site Visit, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Intro (Final), 1977. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Regional Anesthesia, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Renewal & Obstetric Analgesia-Anesthesia, 1978-1983. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Bonica - Site Visit, 1980. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Anesthesia Research Center. Slides, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Argentine Foundation Against Pain. 1991-1992. (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Associated University Physicians. Anesthesiology Incentive Plan, 1976. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Associated University Physicians. Budget Total Department, 1976. (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Associated University Physicians. 1980-1987. (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Associated University Physicians. Revised Retirement Program, 1981. (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. Correspondence with Secretary & Board of Directors, 1975-1978. (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. NYC. Correspondence with participants, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. NYC. Correspondence with staff, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. NYC. Invitations, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. NYC. Program, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. NYC. Publicity, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. Responses to invitations, 1978. (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease. Envelopes, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges. Correspondence, 1964-1977. (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges. 1969-1979. (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges. Correspondence, 1969-1979. (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges. Academic salary ranges, 1970. (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges. Council of ACA (Policy for Biomedical Research), 1970. (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Association of Anesthetists of Great Britain & Ireland. 1986-1990. (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Association of Operating Room Nurses. 1970. (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Correspondence, 1965-1969. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1970. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1971. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1972-1973. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1975-1976. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1976. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1977. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1978. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Delphi Study of Direc. of Research in Anes.& Re..., 1978. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1979-1980. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Meeting, Dallas, TX, 1980. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1981. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Dr. Lassner, 1981. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. 1981-1991. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Directory, 1983. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Associazione Italiana Della Clinica del Dolore. 1988-1989. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - British Obstetric Anaesthetists Association. 1974-1977. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - California Society of Anesthesiologists. Bulletins, 1964-1977. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Casa Italiana. 1989. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - College of Anaesthetists. 1990. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Doctors Hospital of Tacoma. 1962-1963. (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Ehlers Danlos Foundation. 1986-1987. (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - European Association of Anesthesiologists. 1957-1960. (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Federation of American Scientists. 1972-1981. (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center. Program Project on Cancer Pain, 1977-1978. (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital. 1952. (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Guedel Memorial Anesthesia Center. 1967-1979. (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Hawaiian Society of Anesthesiologists. 1957. (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Health and Human Services, Department of. Nationall Center for Health Statistics, Pain Epidural, 1981-1987. (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of. Grants and Awards [publication], 1965. (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of. Grants, 1967. (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of. Fact Book/Comprehensive Health Policy for 70's, 1971. (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of. 1971-1979. (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Indian Hospital. 1958. (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. 1959-1962. (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. 1961-1984. (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Introduction, 1973. (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. ISP, Bonica and Perl, 1973. (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. ISP, Fiscal, 1973. (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Misc. Correspondence, 1973-1978. (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Correspondence on Fundraising, 1974-1977. (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. 1st W.C. NIH Applications, 1975. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. 1st World Pain Congress, 1975. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Newsletters, 1975. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Bylaws, Programs, Newsletters, 1975-1976. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Montreal - Congress & Proposals, 1975-1976. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. President - Elect, 1975-1978. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council Meeting, 1976. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee on Education, 1976-1977. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. German Speaking Pan Society. Annual meeting-Innsbruck, 1976-1977. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Pain - Editorial Board, correspondence, 1976-1979. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. 2nd World Congress on Pain. Scientific Program Committee, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. 2nd World Congress. Publlishing proceedings, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Application NIGMS, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee on Finance, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee on Publications, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council - Treasurers Report, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council Meeting Correspondence, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council Meeting Files, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Exec. Comm., 1977. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Minutes of Committee Meetings, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. President - Elect, John Bonica, M.D., 1977. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Subcommittee on Taxonomy, 1977. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee on Taxonomy, 1977-1978. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. NIDR Application, 1977-1979. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Subcommittee on Taxonomy Correspondence, 1977-1982. (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. 2nd World Congress Data, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Dr. Bonica's Membership, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Executive Committee Council, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Finance Committee, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Italian Chapter, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Montreal, Canada, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. NIDA Final Application II World Congress on Pain, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. NIGMS Application II World Congress on Pain, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. NIH Application II World Congress on Pain, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Pain Congress. General Correspondence, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Pain Congress. Local Arrangements Committee, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Pain Congress. Scientific Program, 1978. (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Directories, 1978, 1980, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Taxonomy Committee, 1978-1979. (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. AISD Directories, 1978-1980. (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Journal of Pain, 1978-1981. (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Financial statement, 1979. (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Misc., 1979. (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Proposed Committees, 1979. (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. President, Correspondence, 1979-1980. (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Newsletter, 1979-1981. (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Newsletter, 1979-1991. (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council, 1980. (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council meeting, 1980. (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. President's Report to Lisbon Council Meeting, 1980. (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Proposed Program for Recent Advances in Management of Pain, 1980. (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Scientific Program Correspondence, 1980-1981. (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. General Correspondence, 1980-1984. (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. APS Meetings During 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee Ethics & Research Correspondence 3rd Congress, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee for Research and Ethical Issues, Corresp, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Correspondence re: Financial Support, 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Correspondence re: Presidential Address, 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council Correspondence, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council Meeting/General Assemblies 3rd Congress, 1981. (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Directory, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Education Committee, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. General Correspondence 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Local Arrangements Correspondence 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Public Information Correspondence 3rd World Congress, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. A.I.S.D., 1982. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee appointments, 1982. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council meeting, Kyoto, Japan, 1982. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Processing of correspondence, 1982. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Public Info Committee - Correspondence, 1982. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Directories, 1982,83,85. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Finance Committee correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Committee on Membership, Correspondence, 1983. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Taxonomy Correspondence, 1983-1990. (Box 56, Folder 14)